总结一些总体思路
Summarize some of the general ideas
我们在这篇文章中讨论过
we've talked about in this reading, which
一般适用于任何语言的编程，
are applicable in general to programming in any language,
但同时也涉及到他们是如何被特别意识到的
but also about how they're specifically realized
使用Java语言特性。
using Java language features.
关键是有几种方法可以做到这一点。
Point is that there are several ways to do it.
重要的是要理解这两个大的想法，
And it's important to understand both the big idea,
就像创造者的操作一样，
like what a creator operation is,
以及在实践中实现这一想法的不同方法。
and the different ways to achieve that idea in practice.
例如，creator操作
So for example, a creator operation
可以在Java中实现为数组列表等构造函数。
can be realized in Java as a constructor such as array list.
它可以实现为静态方法，也称为工厂
It can be realized as a static method, also called a factory
方法，比如collection，singleton list，
method, like collection, singleton list,
或要列出的数组。
or arrays to list.
或者它可以作为一个常数来实现。
Or it can be realized just as a constant.
例如，如果你看大整数类，
So if you look in the big integer class, for example,
有一个0，一个1和一个10。
there is a 0 and a 1 and a 10.
这些只是常数。
And these are just constants.
但他们实际上是创造者。
But they're effectively creators.
当我们谈到ints的时候你也看到了
You saw that as well when we talked about ints
整型文字，0，1，2等等，
and how the integer literals, 0 and 1 and 2 and so forth,
是inttype的创建者。
are creators for the inttype.
对于观察者操作，您可以表示
For an observer operation where you can represent that
作为对特定对象调用的实例方法
as an instance method that you call on a particular object
比如get，你在一个列表的特定实例上调用它，
like get, which you call on a particular instance of a list,
或作为静态方法。
or as a static method.
所以我们可以考虑collections.max，
So we can regard collections.max,
这是一个静态方法
which is a static method that takes
集合——集合可以是任何列表或集合--
a collection-- a collection can be any list or set--
并返回其最大值。
and returns its maximum value.
类似地，生产者操作也可以指实例方法。
Producer operations, similarly, can mean instance method.
举个例子，就像字符串上的trim，
An example is like trim on a string,
删除开头的空白
which removes white space at the beginning
或字符串的结尾并返回新字符串。
or the end of a string and returns a new string.
或者它可以是静态方法。
Or it can be a static method.
所以可修改列表上的集合
So collections on modifiable list
是一个静态方法的示例，该方法是列表的生产者。
is an example of a static method that is a producer for list.
mutator可以是实例方法，也可以是静态方法。
A mutator can be an instance method or a static method.
然后ADT的表示--
And then the representation of an ADT--
在Java中，您表示--通过将
in Java you represent-- you realize that by putting
类中的私有字段。
private fields inside a class.
现在，让我们回去再谈谈测试。
Now, let's go back and talk about testing again.
所以我们在之前的阅读，测试中讨论过
So we talked before in the previous reading, the testing
阅读，关于如何编写测试
reading, about how to write tests
对于单一方法，规范
for a single method, the specification
在单个方法中，为抽象数据构建测试套件
of a single method, to build a test suite for an abstract data
键入。
type.
我们通过创建测试来概括这一点
We generalized that by creating tests
对于它的每个操作
for each of its operations-- each
构成类型的那些方法。
of those methods that make up the type.
现在，这些测试不可避免地相互影响。
Now, these tests inevitably interact with each other.
测试创造者、生产者或变异者的唯一方法
The only way to test the creator or producer or mutator, which
创建对象的新值
either creates a new value of the object
或者改变物体的状态，
or changes the state of the object,
是通过调用结果对象上的观察者
is by calling observers on the resulting objects
看看你期望的效果或结果
to see whether the effects that you expect or the resulting
你从创造者那里得到的东西
object that you got from the creator producer
是你所期望的。
is what you expect.
同样，测试观察者的唯一方法
Similarly, the only way to test an observer
就是为他们创造某种东西
is to create some kind of object for them
观察使用创造者、生产者或变异者观察。
to observe using a creator or a producer or a mutator.
但我们可以用同样的策略
But we can use the same strategies
用于我们单独使用的方法的测试。
for testing that we used with individual methods.
我们只是把它们应用到所有四个操作的输入空间。
We just apply them to the input spaces of all four operations.
所以对于myString类型，你记得
So for a myString type, which you remember
有一个创作者，两个观察者和一个制片人，
had a creator, two observers, and a producer,
我们要做的是划分输入输出
what we would do is partition the input output
每一个的空间。
space of each of those.
所以的值取了一个参数，一个布尔参数。
So value of took one argument, a Boolean argument.
基本上，我们可以把它分成两个可能的输入。
Basically, we can partition that into two possible inputs.
对于长度，你所调用的字符串，
For length, the string that you're calling,
他们调用的myString值，
the myString value that they're calling it on,
长度可能为0、1或大于1。
might have length 0, 1, or greater than 1.
它也可能是一个字符串
It also might be a string produced
有几种不同的方式。
in several different ways.
它可能是由的创建者值生成的字符串。
It might be a string produced by the creator value of.
或者它可能是由子字符串生成的。
Or it might be produced, created by substring.
我们想区分这两个的原因
And the reason we want to distinguish between those two
因为其中一个可能会搞砸
things is because one of these might actually screw up
它创建字符串的方式。
the way it creates the string.
所以测试它们并思考
So it's useful to test them both and think
作为一个分区。
about that as a partition.
我们在[？查拉德？]
And we use that partition in [? charadd ?]
以及对其索引进行分区。
as well as well as partitioning its index.
我们对子串做类似的分区。
And we do similar partitioning on the substring.
然后，我们可以编写一个压缩文本套件
And then, we can write a compact text suite
基本上检查了每个部分
that basically checks off each of the parts
在这些分区中。
of these partitions.
而这，不可避免的，将是--
And that, inevitably, is going to be calling--
两者都将调用多个操作
both going to be calling multiple operations
在每个测试用例中，因为这是我们
in each test case because that's the only way that we
实际上可以检查抽象数据类型的值。
can actually examine the value of an abstract data type.
所以如果测试值为真的话，这就可以抵消了，
So for test value of true, which would check this off,
实际上我们也在检查
we actually also are checking off
其他行动的一些部分。
some of the parts of other operations.
例如，我们在检查
So for example, we were checking off
长度大于1且值为。
length equals greater than 1 and value of.
所以这里有一个测试套件
And so here's a test suite that is
合理的——提供合理的良好的保险
a reasonably-- provides reasonably good coverage
测试策略。
of this testing strategy.
注意，每个测试用例通常
Notice that each test case typically
调用一些可能执行、修改或生成的操作
calls a few operations that might make or modify or produce
类型的新值，然后是
new values of the type and then some operations that
检查类型的对象。
inspect objects of the type.
所以每个测试用例实际上包括
So each test case actually covers
几次行动的一部分。
parts of several operations.